var nombreDelJuego = "CASILLEROS";

var absolutamentetodaslaspreguntas = [
    {
        "pregunta": "0",
        "respuesta": "ARO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "aro",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "1",
        "respuesta": "TE",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "te",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-,t-te,tt-te",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "2",
        "respuesta": "ÑU",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "nu",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-,new-nu,nono-nu,nino-nu",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "3",
        "respuesta": "HUMO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "humo",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-,pomo-humo",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "4",
        "respuesta": "OCA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "oca",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "5",
        "respuesta": "OLA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "ola",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "6",
        "respuesta": "OSO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "oso",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "7",
        "respuesta": "UFO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "ufo",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "8",
        "respuesta": "AJO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "ajo",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "9",
        "respuesta": "BIO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "bio",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "10",
        "respuesta": "TORO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "toro",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "11",
        "respuesta": "DADO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "dado",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "12",
        "respuesta": "DINO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "dino",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "13",
        "respuesta": "TRÉBOL",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "trebol",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "14",
        "respuesta": "DUQUE",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "duque",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "15",
        "respuesta": "CORAZÓN",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "corazon",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "16",
        "respuesta": "TIZA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "tiza",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "17",
        "respuesta": "TIJERA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "tijera",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "18",
        "respuesta": "TEJA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "teja",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "19",
        "respuesta": "TAPIA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "tapia",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "20",
        "respuesta": "NORIA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "noria",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "21",
        "respuesta": "NATA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "nata",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "22",
        "respuesta": "NIÑA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "nina",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "23",
        "respuesta": "NOMO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "nomo",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "24",
        "respuesta": "NOKIA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "nokia",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "25",
        "respuesta": "NILO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "nilo",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "26",
        "respuesta": "NAZI",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "nazi",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "27",
        "respuesta": "NIF",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "nif",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "28",
        "respuesta": "NICHO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "nicho",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "29",
        "respuesta": "NUBE",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "nube",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "30",
        "respuesta": "MORA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "mora",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "31",
        "respuesta": "MOTO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "moto",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "32",
        "respuesta": "MONO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "mono",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "33",
        "respuesta": "MOMIA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "momia",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "34",
        "respuesta": "MOCO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "moco",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "35",
        "respuesta": "MUELA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "muela",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "36",
        "respuesta": "MESA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "mesa",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "37",
        "respuesta": "MAFIA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "mafia",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "38",
        "respuesta": "MAGO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "mago",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "39",
        "respuesta": "MAPA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "mapa",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "40",
        "respuesta": "CURA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "cura",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "41",
        "respuesta": "COHETE",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "cohete",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "42",
        "respuesta": "CONO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "cono",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "43",
        "respuesta": "CAMA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "cama",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "44",
        "respuesta": "CACA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "caca",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "45",
        "respuesta": "COL",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "col",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "46",
        "respuesta": "CASA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "casa",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "47",
        "respuesta": "CAFE",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "cafe",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "48",
        "respuesta": "COCHE",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "coche",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "49",
        "respuesta": "COPA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "copa",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "50",
        "respuesta": "LORO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "loro",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "51",
        "respuesta": "LATA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "lata",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "52",
        "respuesta": "LUNA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "luna",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "53",
        "respuesta": "LIMA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "lima",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "54",
        "respuesta": "LACA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "laca",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "55",
        "respuesta": "LOLA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "lola",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "56",
        "respuesta": "LAZO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "lazo",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "57",
        "respuesta": "ALFA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "alfa",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "58",
        "respuesta": "LECHE",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "leche",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "59",
        "respuesta": "LUPA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "lupa",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "60",
        "respuesta": "SOR",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "sor",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "61",
        "respuesta": "SETA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "seta",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "62",
        "respuesta": "SONY",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "sony",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "63",
        "respuesta": "SUMO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "sumo",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "64",
        "respuesta": "SACA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "saca",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "65",
        "respuesta": "SOL",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "sol",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "66",
        "respuesta": "SESO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "seso",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "67",
        "respuesta": "SOFA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "sofa",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "68",
        "respuesta": "SOGA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "soga",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "69",
        "respuesta": "SOPA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "sopa",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "70",
        "respuesta": "FARO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "faro",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "71",
        "respuesta": "FOTO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "foto",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "72",
        "respuesta": "FINO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "fino",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "73",
        "respuesta": "FAMA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "fama",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "74",
        "respuesta": "FOCA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "foca",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "75",
        "respuesta": "FOLIO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "folio",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "76",
        "respuesta": "FIXO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "fixo",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "77",
        "respuesta": "FOFO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "fofo",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "78",
        "respuesta": "FAJA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "faja",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "79",
        "respuesta": "FBI",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "fbi",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "80",
        "respuesta": "PATO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "pato",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "81",
        "respuesta": "PELO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "pelo",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "82",
        "respuesta": "PINO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "pino",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "83",
        "respuesta": "PUMA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "puma",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "84",
        "respuesta": "POCO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "poco",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "85",
        "respuesta": "PILA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "pila",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "86",
        "respuesta": "PEPA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "pepa",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "87",
        "respuesta": "PAPA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "papa",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "88",
        "respuesta": "POLO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "polo",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "89",
        "respuesta": "BORA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "bora",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "90",
        "respuesta": "BOCA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "boca",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "91",
        "respuesta": "BOTE",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "bote",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "92",
        "respuesta": "BONO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "bono",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "93",
        "respuesta": "BORI",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "bori",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "94",
        "respuesta": "BOOM",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "boom",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "95",
        "respuesta": "BOLA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "bola",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "96",
        "respuesta": "POSA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "posa",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "97",
        "respuesta": "PUPA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "pupa",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "98",
        "respuesta": "PISO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "piso",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "99",
        "respuesta": "PIPO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "pipo",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "00",
        "respuesta": "GAFAS",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "gafas",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "01",
        "respuesta": "RATA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "rata",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "02",
        "respuesta": "RANA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "rana",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "03",
        "respuesta": "REMO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "remo",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "04",
        "respuesta": "ROCA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "roca",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "05",
        "respuesta": "RULO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "rulo",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "06",
        "respuesta": "ROSA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "rosa",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "07",
        "respuesta": "RAFA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "rafa",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "08",
        "respuesta": "PEONZA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "peonza",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "09",
        "respuesta": "ARPA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "arpa",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "ENERO",
        "respuesta": "RELOJ",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "reloj",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "FEBRERO",
        "respuesta": "FLECHAS",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "flechas",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "MARZO",
        "respuesta": "ROBOT",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "robot",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "ABRIL",
        "respuesta": "BOTAS DE AGUA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "botas agua",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "MAYO",
        "respuesta": "BATIDORA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "batidora",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "JUNIO",
        "respuesta": "ARCOIRIS",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "arcoiris",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "JULIO",
        "respuesta": "MICROFONO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "microfono",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "AGOSTO",
        "respuesta": "SOMBRILLA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "sombrilla",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "SEPTIEMBRE",
        "respuesta": "MALETA",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "maleta",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "OCTUBRE",
        "respuesta": "SUBMARINO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "submarino",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "NOVIEMBRE",
        "respuesta": "ANILLO",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "anillo",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    },
    {
        "pregunta": "DICIEMBRE",
        "respuesta": "MUÑECO DE NIEVE",
        "palabrasNecesarias": "muneco de nieve",
        "Ladoyporbuena": "-",
        "reglanemotecnica": ""
    }
];